tuck.com 2019-06-04

# Privacy and Cookie Policy | Tuck Sleep

[Tuck Sleep](https://www.tuck.com/ "Go to Tuck Sleep.") > Privacy and Cookie Policy

Last updated on  January 30, 2019 

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for Tuck.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about new product offerings or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  1. See what data we have about you, if any.
  2. Change/correct any data we have about you.
  3. Have us delete any data we have about you.
  4. Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Security**  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**Updates**  
Tuck has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. If you have any questions pertaining to this privacy policy and its contents, please contact us.

We reserve the right to change, clarify or extend this policy statement at any time.

We may change this policy at any time. Make sure to check the “last updated” date at the top of this page to see when our policy was last revised.

**What is a cookie?**  
Cookies are small text files that are sent from a website’s computers to a user’s browser, where it is stored on the user’s computer/device hard drive. Our cookies store a small amount of information on your device about your visit to our site, but they can’t access any information you didn’t provide.

We may also use “web beacons” on tuck.com that tell us whether you have visited certain web pages or have received certain messages. These are generally a one-pixel image that is retrieved from a remote website that verifies a user’s viewing of a web page or message. Web beacons allow us to learn whether you came to our website from certain advertisements on third-party websites, measure effectiveness of marketing campaigns and ultimately enhance our overall website performance. Additionally, we can use web beacons to relate your viewing of a web page or message to other information about you such as web behavior and demographic information.

We use both first and third-party cookies. First party cookies are cookies we place and access, whereas third party cookies are accessed by some of our third party vendors.

Feel free to disallow our use of cookies in your browser settings. If you do this, however, some website functions may not work properly.

**Cookies we use**  
Below is a list and description of all the various cookies we use on our site.

  * **_Analytics Cookies_**  
Analytics cookies gather information about your use of the site, allowing us to see broader user behavior and improve our site accordingly. These cookies tell us things like what pages have the highest traffic rates, where people go from certain pages, and which pages are more likely to result in users leaving our site.
  * **_Essential Cookies_**  
Essential cookies are a site’s basic memory and are necessary for the site to function. These are the cookies responsible for remembering which page you last visited, for example.
  * **_Advertising Cookies_**  
Advertising cookies are intended to collect information about your web behavior in order to provide targeted advertisements.
  * **_Social Media Cookies_**  
Social Media cookies are what allows you to share our content on various social media platforms. For example, our giveaways rely on social media cookies. These cookies can also be used for advertising.

**How to Manage Cookie Preferences**  
If you’d prefer not have accept cookies from tuck.com or any other site, you can turn cookies off in your browser. This may interfere with your use of various interactive features on our site. You can find information on how to manage cookies on the following browsers in the below links:
